<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 20:53:57 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Thought Qi Gong</title>
      <link>/small-thought-qi-gong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/small-thought-qi-gong/</guid>
      <description>Syllabus  Qi Gong Standing Posture Warm Up – classic movements to loosen joints, fascia and marrow Jing Gong Sound Healing Zen Breathing Qi Gong Qi Manipulation I Fong Song Gong Qi Gong Qi Manipulation II Anapanasati Meditation Shen Gong Wing Chun Gong Fu Posture – Yee Gee Kim Yang Ma Wing Chun Small Thought I – Secret Energy Sounds Wing Chun Small Thought II – Meridian Opening Wing Chun Small Thought III – Basic Hands Partner Training for Hand Techniques – Wing Chun Hands at Distances Partner Training for Energy and Grounding – Wing Chun Sticky Hands (Dan Chi Sao)  Overview of the Course The course is taught as a 12 week program consisting of 1 to 2 hour lessons, covering the Yin side of Wing Chun Qi Gong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 20:53:57 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!
My name is Jordan Del-Grande, and I live in Canberra, Australia. In 2012, I was endorsed as a Sifu of Wing Chun Qi Gong (詠春氣功) directly by Sifu Gregory Choi, (previously Tsoi Shiu Kwong or Choy Siu Kwong), a closed-door student of Grand Master Yip Man (葉問宗師).
My interpretation of Sifu is someone who acts as a teacher and guide to the student, since a guide has already traveled the path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qi Gong Benefits</title>
      <link>/benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 20:53:57 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/benefits/</guid>
      <description>Discover Qi Gong Stage Quickly – Don’t wast your time Qi Gong can best be translated as Life Force Cultivation. This Force or Qi can be used for multiple purposes, but within the Wing Chun courses, it is used for either Healing or Hurting (‘Martial Art’). Hence, Wing Chun Qi Gong (詠春氣功) is a the Way of Understanding Life Force and its application to Healing and Martial Arts.
The Wing Chun Qi Gong (詠春靈通氣功) course is direct, simple and scientific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donations</title>
      <link>/donations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 20:53:57 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/donations/</guid>
      <description>All Donations Welcome Jordan has spent tens of thousands of dollars in the learning of this wonderful art. He has made a bodhisattva vow to assist all beings in the learning of meditation, qi gong, healing, kung fu and virtue. As such, he provides a majority of the material for the benefit of this generation and the next for free.
In order to keep these resources online, we only ask for a small donation, such as what you would pay for a cup of coffee, as all donations go towards the the online support of web hosting obligations and further improvements in course material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 22:17:00 +0001</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/history/</guid>
      <description>Roots in Shaolin Legend says that 500 years ago during the Ming Dynasty (明朝) in mainland China, the Abbess Ng Mui (五梅) was one of the Five Elders of the Shaolin Temple (少林寺). The Five Elders included the Grand Master Ji Shim (至善禪師), Bak Mai with White Eyebrows (白眉道人), Fung Dao Tak (馮道德), Miu Hin (苗顯) and Ng Mui. Ng Mui reportedly lived outside of the temple in her own hut, where she met privately with these masters learning the secretive Kung Fu (功夫) and Qi Gong (氣功) knowledge of Shaolin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syllabus</title>
      <link>/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Wing Chun Qi Gong is an all inclusive Energy Cultivation, Kung Fu, Meditative and Healing School, with the lineage and practices dating back thousands of years across thousands of schools, traditions and continents such as India, China, and Tibet.
It’s very difficult to find one school that has all this to offer, instead of waiting years for the master to trust you before passing the knowledge along. Or worse still, false teachers manipulating students in master-slave relathipship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>